Finding Aid for Office of the Vice President and Secretary of the University (University of Michigan) records, 1935-2007
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - Branch Campuses
    - UM Flint
      - Enrollment Market Analysis, 2000 (Box 12)
      - General, 2004-2005 (Box 12)
      - General, 1996-2004, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Nelms, Charles, 1994 (Box 12)
      - Tuition Petition, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Executive Officers
    - Compensation Package, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 1995-2002 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, July 2004-September 2005 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, September -- December, 2005 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 12)
    - Meetings, July -- December, 2006 (Box 12)
    - Retreat/Dino Biris, 2003-2004 (Box 12)
  - Health Systems
    - Brighton Health Center, 1986-1988 (Box 13)
    - Cancer and Geriatrics Centers: Planning, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Cardiovascular Center, 2002-2004 (Box 13)
    - Considerations on Restructuring of UM Medical Center, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Forsyth, John D., 1985-1996 (Box 13)
    - Forsyth, John D., 1996 (Box 13)
    - General Files, 1999-2003 (Box 13)
    - Hospitals, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - Hospitals, 1987-1993 (Box 13)
    - Hospitals, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Hospitals and Health Centers, 2000-2003 (Box 13)
    - Hospitals and Health Centers, 2004 (Box 13)
    - Hospitals and Health Centers, 2005 (Box 13)
    - Hospitals and Health Centers, 2006 (Box 13)
    - Hospital Executive Board Summaries, 1999-2001 (Box 13)
    - Hospital Executive Board Summaries, 2001-2006, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Hospitals -- Organ Transplant Program, 1984-1988 (Box 13)
    - Hospital Revenue Bonds, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Maternal/Child Health Center, 1990 (Box 13)
    - M-Care HMO, 1975-1989 (Box 13)
    - MEDC Meeting, 1999-2001 (Box 13)
    - Medical Center Restructuring -- Shields Presentation, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Medical Center Issues, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Medical Center Meetings, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Medical Center Visits, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Medical Malpractice, 1969-2001 (Box 14)
    - Medical School, 1973-1978, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Medical School, 1996-2003 (Box 14)
    - Shields, Geoffrey, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Zuidema, George D., 1978-1993 (Box 14)
  - Life Sciences Institute
    - Articles, 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    - Briefing Book, 1999, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Facilities, 1999-2000 (Box 14)
    - General Files -- Articles, 1999 (Box 14)
    - General Files, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
    - General Files, 1999 (Box 14)
    - Group Strategy, 2000-2002 (Box 14)
    - Lab Design, 1999 (Box 15)
    - Life Sciences Corridor, 1999-2000 (Box 15)
    - Life Sciences Corridor, 2000-2002, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Life Sciences Initiative, 1998-199 (Box 15)
    - Life Science Initiatives May 2000 Report to Campus, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
    - Reports, 2000-2005 (Box 15)
  - President's Office
    - Bollinger, Lee, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Duderstadt, James, 1988-1996 (Box 15)
    - Neal, Homer, 1996 (Box 15)
    - President's Advisory Group, 2002-2004, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - President's Club Members, 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - President's Council Survey: State Appropriations for Higher Education, 2000 (Box 15)
    - President's Dinners (Planning: Facilities/Development/Academic Initiatives), 2001 (Box 15)
    - President's Information Revolution Commission Report, 2001 (Box 15)
    - President's Office Tracking, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Presidents' Salaries, 1998-2006 (Box 15)
    - President's Speeches, 1999-2006, 2 folders (Box 15)
      (includes cassette tapes)
    - President's Staff Meetings, 2002-2004 (Box 15)
    - Retirement Garden Party, 1996 (Box 15)
  - Bylaws Section 14.06
    - Sexual Orientation, 1983-1989 (Box 15)
    - Sexual Orientation Letters, 1994, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Sexual Orientation Opposition Letters, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Sexual Orientation Support Letters, 1994, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - University Finances
    - Budget, 1975-1991, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Budget, 1999-2003, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 16)
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - Budget, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Budget, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Budget Communications, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
    - Budget Detail, 1999-2000 (Box 16)
    - Budget Detail, 2001-2002 (Box 16)
    - Budget Discussions, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Budget -- General Fund, 2002-2006 (Box 16)
    - Budget Materials, 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Budget Planning, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Budget -- Program Outcomes for Universities, 1998-2001 (Box 17)
    - Consolidated Financial Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 17)
    - Financial Reporting Changes/Accounting Standards, 1999-2003 (Box 17)
    - Invested Funds, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Investment Advisory Committee, 2000-2002, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Investment Advisory Committee, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Investment Advisory Committee, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Investment Advisory Committee, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Investment Office, 2001-2004 (Box 17)
    - Investments, 1970-1994 (Box 17)
    - State Budget, 1998-2003, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - State Budget Appropriations, 2004-2005 (Box 17)
    - State Budget Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 17)
    - University Audit and Consolidated Financial Statements, 2004-2005 (Box 17)
    - University Investment Commission, 2002-2005 (Box 17)
  - General Files
    - "A Guide to the University of Michigan Activities in Metropolitan Detroit," 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    - "A Survey of Michigan Attitudes on the Public Colleges and Universities in the State" -- Draft Preliminary Report, 1984 (Box 18)
    - AATA (Ann Arbor Transportation Authority)-UM Partnership, 2001-2005 (Box 18)
    - Academic Attire, 1935-1989 (Box 18)
    - Academic Calendar, 1992-2004 (Box 18)
    - Academic Program Group, 1999-2003 (Box 18)
    - Academic Program Group, 2004 (Box 18)
    - Academic Program Group, 2004-2005 (Box 18)
    - Academic Progress Committee (Extension of SACUA), 2003 (Box 18)
    - ACTA (American Council of Trustees and Alumni), 2004 (Box 18)
    - Administrative Staff Trends, 1991 (Box 18)
    - Admissions -- General, 1987-2000 (Box 18)
    - Admissions, 1999-2000 (Box 18)
    - Admissions, 2001-2003 (Box 18)
    - Admissions (New Evaluation Process), 2003 (Box 18)
    - Admissions, 2004-2005 (Box 18)
    - AFSCME, 1999-2000 (Box 18)
    - AFSCME -- Arbitration, 1990 (Box 18)
    - AFSCME/Hospital Visitor's Cafeteria, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Agreements, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Alcohol/Drug Prevention, 1998-2005 (Box 18)
    - Alumni Association, 1976-1994 (Box 18)
    - Alumni Association, 1999-2000 (Box 18)
    - Alumni Association, 2000-2004 (Box 18)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1984-1991 (Box 18)
    - American Customer Satisfaction Index (ACSI), 2003 (Box 18)
    - American Disabilities Act, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - Anderson, John, 1996-2001 (Box 37)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2076 ]
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival, 1978-1993 (Box 18)
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 19)
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival -- Meeting Agenda/Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 19)
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival -- Parking, 1999-2004 (Box 19)
    - Arbor Heights Facility (Children's Center), 2001 (Box 19)
    - Archives: Regents: Bentley Library, 1982-1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Arthur F. Thurnau Professorship, 1988-1999 (Box 19)
    - Articles, 1998-2002, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Arboretum, 1995-1997 (Box 19)
    - Association of Board Secretaries, 1978-1996 (Box 19)
    - Association of Board Secretaries, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Association of Board Secretaries, 1998-2004 (Box 19)
    - Association of Governing Boards, 1959-1971 (Box 19)
    - Association of Governing Boards, 1972-1982 (Box 19)
    - Association of Governing Boards, 1983-1991, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Association of Governing Boards, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
    - Association of Governing Boards, 2003-2004 (Box 19)
    - Audio Visual Education Materials Policy, 1973 (Box 20)
    - Audit Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 20)
    - Audits, 1999-2004 (Box 20)
    - Audits Office, 1990-1995 (Box 20)
    - Autonomy, 1988-1990 (Box 20)
    - Avis Properties, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Bagnoud, Francois-Xavier, 1992 (Box 20)
    - Baha'i Club, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Ballot Initiatives, 2003-2004 (Box 20)
    - Ballots, 1999-2000 (Box 20)
    - Bentley Library Executive Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 20)
    - Betz, David, 1997 (Box 37)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2072 ]
    - Boylan, Paul C., 1993 (Box 20)
    - Boy Scouts, 2000-2003 (Box 20)
    - Brinkerhoff, James F., 1976-1988, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Burton Tower (Charles Baird Carillon), 1983-1986 (Box 20)
    - Business School, 2002 (Box 20)
    - Butler, Joseph, 1987 (Box 37)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2062 ]
    - Butts, Thomas A., 1991 (Box 20)
    - Bylaws -- Preface, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Camp Knight, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Campus Master Plan, 1997-1999 (Box 20)
    - Campus Safety Task Force/Report, 1990-1997 (Box 20)
    - Cantor, Courtney, 1998-2000 (Box 20)
    - Career Development Fund, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Carl D. Bradley Shipwreck, 1997 (Box 20)
    - Carnegie Foundation, 2001 (Box 20)
    - Center of Champions, 1989 (Box 20)
    - Central Campus Planning, 2005 (Box 20)
    - Center for Equal Opportunity, 2003 (Box 20)
    - Center for the Education of Women, 1993-2000, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Center for the Education of Women, 2001-2005 (Box 20)
    - Center for Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences (CGLAS), 2001-2002 (Box 20)
    - Center for Institutional Diversity, 2003 (Box 20)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT), 1993-2003 (Box 20)
    - Chang Studies/OVPR, 1998-2001 (Box 21)
    - Chang Studies/OVPR, 2001, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Charter of the University of Michigan, undated (Box 21)
    - Cheerleading, 1987 (Box 21)
    - Cherry Commission Report, 2004 (Box 21)
    - Child Care, 1997-2002 (Box 21)
    - Children's Better Health Institute, 1998-1999 (Box 21)
    - Childs, Cecilia, 1990-1999 (Box 21)
    - China -- Central University for Nationalities (CUN), 1999 (Box 21)
    - Chronological File, Jan-June 1995 (Box 21)
    - Chronological File, July-Dec 1995 (Box 21)
    - Chronological File, Jan-July 1996 (Box 21)
    - Chronological File, Aug-Dec 1996 (Box 21)
    - Chronological File, 1997 (Box 21)
    - Chronological File, Nov 1998-Jan 1999 (Box 21)
    - Chronological File, Feb 1999-Dec 1999 (Box 22)
    - Chronological File, 2000 (Box 22)
    - CIC (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) -- Academic Leadership Program, 1999-2001 (Box 22)
    - CIC (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) Report, 2004 (Box 22)
    - City of Ann Arbor, 1970-1993 (Box 22)
    - City of Ann Arbor -- Oakway Road Realignment, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Citizens Queries (CQ)
      - Admissions, 1999-2003 (Box 22)
      - Alumni Association, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Athletics, 1999-2003 (Box 22)
      - Bentley, 1999-2004 (Box 22)
      - Facilities and Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 22)
      - Finances, 1999-2002 (Box 22)
      - General Counsel, 1999-2000 (Box 37)
      - Internet, 1999-2003 (Box 22)
      - Medical Center, 1998-2001 (Box 22)
      - Medical Center, 1999-2003 (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous, 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000-2002 (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous, 2003-2004 (Box 22)
      - Patents, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Residency, 1999-2000 (Box 22)
      - ROTC, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Student Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 22)
      - Student Issues, 1998-2002 (Box 23)
      - Tuition/Fees, 1999-2002 (Box 23)
      - Tuition/Fees, 2002-2003 (Box 23)
      - UM-Flint, 1999-2003 (Box 23)
    - Classified Research, 1986-1991 (Box 23)
    - Clements Library, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Climate and Character Documents, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Codes of Conduct (various Colleges), 1989 (Box 23)
    - Cohen, Carl, 2000 (Box 23)
    - College Board, 2000 (Box 23)
    - College of Engineering, 1975-1991 (Box 23)
    - College of Literature, Science, and the Arts, 1973-1994 (Box 23)
    - College of Pharmacy, 1965-1975 (Box 23)
    - College of Architecture and Urban Planning, undated (Box 23)
    - Commencement, 1990 (Box 23)
    - Commencement, 1998-2001, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Commencement Speeches/Scripts, 1995-1999 (Box 23)
    - Committee on Economic Status of Faculty (CESF), 1974-1988 (Box 23)
    - Committee on Economic Status of Faculty (CESF), 1988-1989 (Box 23)
    - Complaints, 1990-1992 (Box 23)
    - Computer and Computer Centers, 1975-1993 (Box 23)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1996 (Box 23)
    - Consent Agenda, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Convocation, 1990 (Box 23)
    - Convocation, 1999-2001 (Box 23)
    - Copyrights -- Arthur, E.A., 1998-1999 (Box 23)
    - Cosovich, John (Vice President), 1979-1991 (Box 23)
    - Deans, Directors, and Department Heads -- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 24)
    - Degrees -- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964-1995 (Box 24)
    - Department of Communications, 1994-1995 (Box 24)
    - Department of Public Safety Luncheon, 2000 (Box 24)
    - Detroit Principles, 1992 (Box 24)
    - Detroit Center, 2004-2005 (Box 24)
    - Detroit Health Services Research Initiative (DHSRI), 2000-2003 (Box 24)
    - Detroit Public Schools, 2000 (Box 24)
    - Development, 1999-2006 (Box 24)
    - Development Campaign 2004 -- The Michigan Difference, 2004 (Box 24)
    - Development Campaign Facilities Project, 2003 (Box 24)
    - Development -- Campaign Related, 2001-2002 (Box 24)
    - Development Fund-Raising Campaign, 2000-2001 (Box 24)
    - Diag Shanties, 1982-1990 (Box 24)
    - Diploma, 1963-1987 (Box 24)
    - Distance Learning, 1999-2001, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Distance Learning Tuition, 2000-2003 (Box 24)
    - Diverse CD, 1998 (Box 24)
    - Diversity, 1990-1999 (Box 24)
    - Diversity, 2000-2007 (Box 24)
    - Diversity Summit, 2004 (Box 24)
    - Divestiture in South Africa, 1988-1992 (Box 24)
    - Domestic Violence Policy, 2003-2007 (Box 24)
    - Duderstadt, Ann, 1992 (Box 24)
    - Duderstadt, James J., 1980-1993 (Box 24)
    - Eating Disorders, 2000 (Box 24)
    - Eckstein, Robert, 1991 (Box 24)
    - Economic Outlook, 2000-2004 (Box 24)
    - Eisenberg, J., 1998-1999 (Box 24)
    - Employment Grievances, 1990-1992 (Box 24)
    - Endowment Fund, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Energy, 1977-1987 (Box 25)
    - Enrollment, 1999-2003 (Box 25)
    - Ensuring Junior Faculty Become Senior Faculty, 2000 (Box 25)
    - Environmental Issues, 2003-2005 (Box 25)
    - Environmental Task Force, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Evaluation of Administration Proposal, 2003-2004 (Box 25)
    - Executive Vice President for Medical Affairs (EVPMA) Candidate, 2003 (Box 25)
    - Executive Vice President-Chief Financial Officer (EVP-CFO) Search, 2003 (Box 25)
    - External Relations Group, 2000-2005, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Facilities, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
    - Facilities and Operations, 2003 (Box 25)
    - Faculty -- General, 2001-2006 (Box 25)
    - Faculty Handbook, 2001 (Box 25)
    - Faculty -- Outstanding, 2004 (Box 25)
    - Faculty -- Staff Housing, 1991 (Box 25)
    - Faculty: Status of Women and Minorities, 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Faculty Work Life Study, 1999 (Box 25)
    - FASAP (Faculty and Staff Assistance Program)
      - Advisory Board, 1998-2002, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Advisory Board, 1999-2001 (Box 25)
      - Advisory Board, 2003-2004, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Fathom/Columbia, 2000-2001 (Box 25)
    - Fee Approval, 1998-1999 (Box 25)
    - Fifth Generation Systems (Software), 1991 (Box 25)
    - Finance and Capital Projects Committee, 2003-2004, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Finance and Capital Projects Committee, 2007 (Box 26)
    - Fink, Jason, 2000 (Box 26)
    - Financial Aid, 1974-1992 (Box 26)
    - Fireside Chats (Regents/Students), 2002 (Box 26)
    - Fitness for Duty, 1999-2000 (Box 26)
    - Flags, 1955-2000 (Box 26)
    - Fleming, Robben W., 1967-1988 (Box 26)
    - Flint Auto World, 1982-1984 (Box 26)
    - FOIA, 1992-1997 (Box 26)
    - FOIA, 2002-2003 (Box 26)
    - FOIA, 2003 (Box 26)
    - FOIA, 2003-2004 (Box 26)
    - FOIA, 2004-2007 (Box 26)
    - FOIA -- Presidential Search, 2002, 3 folders (Box 26)
    - FOIA -- Regents, 2002-2003, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - FOIA -- Reports/Tracking Log, 2004-2006 (Box 27)
    - Fort Meigs Treaty Petition, 1975 (Box 27)
    - Freedom of Speech, 1975-1994 (Box 27)
    - "From Invisibility to Inclusion: Opening the Doors for Lesbian and Gay Men at the University of Michigan," 1991 (Box 27)
    - Gallagher, Keith B., 1998-2000 (Box 37)
    - Gender Equity, 2001-2003 (Box 27)
    - Gender Language, 1988-1989 (Box 27)
    - General Correspondence
      - A, 1979-1993 (Box 27)
      - B, 1975-1990 (Box 27)
      - C, 1970-1989, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - D, 1986-1992 (Box 27)
      - E, 1975-1992 (Box 27)
      - F, 1969-2001 (Box 27)
      - H, 1979-1998 (Box 27)
      - I, 1975-1992 (Box 27)
      - J, 1963-1989 (Box 27)
      - K, 1964-1991 (Box 27)
      - L, 1971-1996 (Box 27)
      - M, 1980-1992 (Box 27)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 27)
      - N, 1973-1991 (Box 27)
      - O, 1971-1994 (Box 27)
      - P, 1979-1992 (Box 28)
      - S, 1965-1998, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - T, 1975-1993 (Box 28)
      - U, 1985-1994 (Box 28)
    - General Counsel, 1985-1994 (Box 37)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2094 ]
    - General Counsel, 1998-2001 (Box 37)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2101 ]
    - General Counsel, 2002-2006 (Box 37)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2106 ]
    - General Motors Institute, 1981 (Box 28)
    - Geography Department Discontinuation, 1981 (Box 28)
    - Geriatrics Center, 2001 (Box 28)
    - Gifts, 1991 (Box 28)
    - Glaxo Smith Kline, 2001 (Box 28)
    - Global Warming, 2001 (Box 28)
    - Goldberg Case (Sociology), 1993 (Box 28)
    - Gong, Siew Ging, 1999 (Box 28)
    - Gordon Hall, 2001, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Governmental Activities, Public Service Bylaw 5.13, 1976-1987 (Box 28)
    - Graduate Employees Organization, 1975-1991 (Box 28)
    - Grand Haven Aquarium Project, 1994-1995 (Box 28)
    - Granger, Daniel, 1998 (Box 37)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2073 ]
    - Grievances, 1989-1990 (Box 28)
    - Grievances, 2002-2003 (Box 28)
    - Ground Breakage -- Central Campus Building Projects, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Habitat for Humanity, 1995 (Box 29)
    - Hamele, Alice, 1990-1999 (Box 37)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2099 ]
    - Harrison, Walter, 1989-1994 (Box 29)
    - Health Scholars Program, 2001 (Box 29)
    - Henry Russell Awards, 1980-1997 (Box 29)
    - Henry Russell Lecturer, 1974-1999 (Box 29)
    - Hensel, Mary D., 1990-1995 (Box 29)
    - Higher Education Price Index, 1989 (Box 29)
    - Hillard, Sam, 1999 (Box 29)
    - Hi-Po (Hazardous Waste), 2000 (Box 29)
    - Holidays, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
    - Holocaust Memorial, 1993 (Box 29)
    - HOPE Project, 1999 (Box 29)
    - Housing, 1990-1999, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Housing, 2000-2004, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Human Resources, 1999-2003 (Box 29)
    - Human Resources, 2003-2004 (Box 29)
    - Human Resources, 2004-2005 (Box 29)
    - Human Resources, 2005-2006 (Box 29)
    - Imagining America: Artists and Scholars in Public Life -- Julie Ellison, 1999-2002 (Box 29)
    - Indemnification Policy, 1995 (Box 29)
    - Indian Concerns -- Native American Graves Repatriation and Protection Act, 1997 (Box 29)
    - Information Systems, 1991-1992 (Box 29)
    - Information Technology Division (ITD), 1999-2000 (Box 29)
    - Inglis House, 1996 (Box 29)
    - Inglis, James, 1933-1992 (Box 29)
    - Internal Audits, 1983-1992 (Box 29)
    - International Committee, 1991 (Box 29)
    - International Families Outreach Project (IFOP), 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), 1998 (Box 30)
    - International Women's Day 2000 Confronting Global Violence Against Women (Seminar), 2000 (Box 30)
    - Investor Responsibility Research Center, 1988 (Box 30)
    - Issue Selling, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Jackson, Audrey, 2000-2001 (Box 30)
    - Jackson, James -- "A National Study on Black Americans and Other Racial and Ethnic Groups in the Diversifying America of the 21st Century," 2001 (Box 30)
    - Johnson, Harold, 1976-1994 (Box 30)
    - Kennedy, Richard L., 1956-1994, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Kennedy, Richard L. -- Party, 1992-1994 (Box 30)
    - Krause Street Parking Lots/Argus Buildings, 1983-1988 (Box 30)
    - Kuumba, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Labor Update Meeting, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Lake Superior State University, 1988 (Box 30)
    - Law School, 1965-1991 (Box 30)
    - Learning Technology Initiative: Current Status and Goals for 2000, 1999 (Box 30)
    - Leases, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Lehman, Jeffrey, 2003 (Box 30)
    - License Agreement, 1991 (Box 30)
    - Licenses, 1977-1992 (Box 30)
    - Living-Learning Program, circa 1998 (Box 30)
    - Living and Learning Programs -- Review Group, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Living Wage/Employment Policies, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Mandela Degree Petitions, undated (Box 30)
    - Mandela, Nelson, 1986-1987 (Box 30)
    - Manufacturer's Code of Conduct, circa 1999 (Box 30)
    - Martha Cook Building Board of Governors, 1991-1994 (Box 30)
    - Martin Luther King Commemoration, 1975-1992 (Box 30)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1999-2002 (Box 30)
    - Martinez, David (racism complaint), 2002 (Box 30)
    - Matlock, John, 1996 (Box 30)
    - Matthaei Botanical Gardens, 1992 (Box 30)
    - Media Hits, 2002 (Box 30)
    - Media Managers, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
    - Medicare Audit, 1997 (Box 30)
    - Memberships in Professional Organizations, 1977-1989 (Box 30)
    - Meningitis, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
    - Mental Health Resources, 2003-2005 (Box 30)
    - MERIT Proposal, 1987 (Box 30)
    - Merit Scholars, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Michigan Agenda for Women, 1994-1996 (Box 30)
    - Michigan Awareness Program, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Michigan Daily, 1989-1991 (Box 30)
    - Michigan Higher Education, 1984-1988 (Box 31)
    - Michigan House of Representatives, 1959-1980 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Information Systems and Services, 1988 (Box 31)
    - Michigan League, 1973-1994 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Mandate, 1988-1996 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Mandate, 1990-1997 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Memorial -- Phoenix Project (MMPP), 1997-1999 (Box 31)
    - Michigan State University, 1954-1980 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA), 1980-1989 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA), 1989-1996 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Student Assembly -- Year End Report, 2002 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA) -- Projects, 1999-2001, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Michigan Union, 1962-1994 (Box 31)
    - Michigan Women's Hall of Fame Banquet, 1988 (Box 31)
    - Military Service, 1940-1991 (Box 31)
    - Minority Reports, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Minority Students, 1978-1989 (Box 31)
    - Minye, Leslie, 1978-1984 (Box 37)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2059 ]
    - Mission Statement -- University of Michigan, 1989 (Box 31)
    - MIT President's Conference on Equity, 2001-2002 (Box 32)
    - MIT Study/Project, 2001-2002 (Box 32)
    - Moeller, Gary, 1994-1995 (Box 32)
    - Monts, Lester P., 1993 (Box 32)
    - Moore vs UM (ITD Case), 1992-1993 (Box 37)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2093 ]
    - M-Pathways Student Administration Implementation, 2000 (Box 32)
    - Naked Mile, 1999-2000 (Box 32)
    - Naming of Buildings, Roadways, and Other Facilities, 1966-1994 (Box 32)
    - Narratives of Compassion in Organizations by Frost/Dutton/Worline/Wilson, 2000 (Box 32)
    - NML (New Millennium Leaders) Scholars Program, 2004 (Box 32)
    - News Information Services (NIS), 2000 (Box 32)
    - News Releases -- Non-UM, 1998 (Box 32)
    - Nickens Award, 2001 (Box 32)
    - North Campus Hazardous Waste Facility, 1991 (Box 32)
    - North Central Association, 1991 (Box 32)
    - Novello, Antonia -- Commencement, 1996 (Box 32)